<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Roberto PM</title><link>https://roberto.pm/feed/rss.xml</link><description>My latest blog posts.</description><atom:link href="https://roberto.pm/feed/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 05:45:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://roberto.pm/blog/hello_world.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post on this little platform that I've built.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I will probably detail its inner workings in a future article. Suffice to say&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;it's the very opposite of refined, and if I hesitate to call it ugly, it is&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;only because I made it simple enough that I don't hate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are several reasons for me to have made this. The most prominent one of&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;course is as a mean of procrastination. Another reason would be the great&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;dislike that I have developed towards the modern internet. For most people,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;what would be called as a “web presence”, is usually attained through the ever&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;famous _colossi_ of the web. While information technologies are becoming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;increasingly available and omni-present in everyday life, net-citizens are less&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the “home-owners” than they used to be. In many ways we have become like digital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;cattle. It is not immediately apparent how we are paying for the spaces that we&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;rent, but we are paying nonetheless, were it be with our privacy, security, or&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;even sanity...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, as I started to get sucked into the tech world, I have noticed a bunch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;of personal websites, more or less minimal, that I enjoy reading regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I keep many of them in my list of feeds, and even if those, as a general rule,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;are vastly more interesting than what'll write, I told myself that I'd try&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;doing something similar.&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://roberto.pm/blog/hello_world.html</guid></item></channel></rss>