<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Roberto PM</title><link>https://roberto.pm/feed/rss.xml</link><description>My latest blog posts.</description><atom:link href="https://roberto.pm/feed/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 17:16:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://roberto.pm/blog/hello_world.html</link><description>I guess this is the inaugural content for this platform.&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;I will probably detail its inner workings in a future article. Suffice to say it’s the very opposite of refined, and if I hesitate to call it ugly, it is only because I made it simple enough so that I don’t outright hate it.&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;There are several reasons for me to have made this. The most prominent one of course is as a mean of procrastination. Another reason would be the great dislike that I have developed towards the modern internet. For most people, what would be called as a “web presence”, is usually attained through the ever famous &lt;em&gt;colossi&lt;/em&gt; of the web. While information technologies are becoming increasingly available and omnipresent in everyday life, net-citizens are less the “home-owners” than they used to be. In many ways we have become like digital cattle. It is maybe not immediately apparent how we are paying for the spaces on which we stand, but we are paying nonetheless, were it with our privacy, security, or even our sanity…&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Lastly, as I started to get sucked into the tech world, I have noticed a bunch of personal websites, more or less minimal, that I enjoy reading regularly. I keep many of them in my list of feeds, and even if those, as a general rule, are vastly more interesting than what’ll write, I told myself that I’d try doing something similar.&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><guid isPermaLink="false">https://roberto.pm/blog/hello_world.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 05:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>